<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Greek Mythology</title>
    <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Greek Mythology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:14:32 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iriss04.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:14:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>This website is a part of project assignment B in the course 02805 - Social Graphs and interactions at DTU. Here we will present our idea and analyses to the world! We will with this website tell the story about our dataset and what we&amp;rsquo;ve learned.
Here is our video submission for part A of this assignment.

To download our dataset press here.
To download our explainer notebook press here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dataset</title>
      <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:46:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/data/</guid>
      <description>About the dataset The dataset we&amp;rsquo;re exploring is from Greek mythology. The data used in this project was extracted from a Fandom wiki containing all kinds of information about characters of Greek mythology.
The dataset we extracted includes information about many categories of greek mythology. To name a few we have for example Gods, Heroes, Creatures and Peoples. The dataset includes which characters belong to which categories and text about each of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Network and basic stats</title>
      <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 23:45:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/network/</guid>
      <description>In this post you will see the network of Greek mythology we created. How the information from the Fandom wiki was extracted is detailed in the dataset post.
The network After getting all the characters, their texts and their links the Giant Connected Component (GCC) was plotted. The characters, nodes, is given different colours to make it more visually pretty and there is added edges in between to see which characters has links to which.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis</title>
      <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 22:46:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/analysis/</guid>
      <description>For this part of the project we go in deeper analysis of the dataset. Here we will not go deep into how the analysis was performed, that information is available in our explainer notebook, which can be downloaded here. Here you will see the word clouds we created. Finding communities and calculate their TF-IDF. Then finally sentiment of the created communities.
Word clouds Word Clouds are a very fun way to get to know your dataset better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explainer notebook</title>
      <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/notebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 15:05:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/notebook/</guid>
      <description>For this project we created an explainer notebook.
In the explainer notebook you can find description of all the tools used in this assignment and the whole code.
You can find the notebook here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
