<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Greek Mythology</title>
    <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Greek Mythology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:14:32 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iriss04.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:14:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>This website is a part of project assignment B in the course 02805 - Social Graphs and interactions at DTU. Here we will present our idea and analyses to the world! We will with this website tell the story about our dataset and what we&amp;rsquo;ve learned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dataset</title>
      <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 15:06:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/data/</guid>
      <description>About the dataset The dataset we&amp;rsquo;re exploring is from Greek mythology. The data used in this project was extracted from a Fandom page containing all kinds of information about characters of Greek mythology.
The dataset we extracted includes information about many categories of greek mythology. To name a few we have for example Gods, Heroes, Creatures and Peoples. The dataset includes which characters belong to which categories and text about each of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Network</title>
      <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 13:45:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/network/</guid>
      <description>The populace thronged the avenues of the law courts in particular, because they knew that the Flemish ambassadors, who had arrived two days previously, intended to be present at the representation of the mystery, and at the election of the Pope of the Fools, which was also to take place in the grand hall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Characters</title>
      <link>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 13:45:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iriss04.github.io/posts/characters/</guid>
      <description>There are XXX number of characters in the Greek Mythology network. In this project there are XXX nodes and XXX links. The largest node is XXX with XXX number og links.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
